Training length: 1559
Testing length: 520
Number of training examples: 1469 Hence effective training length: 1469 days
Number of testing examples: 430 Hence effective testing length: 430 days
This is train Environment with 1560 rows and 11 columns
ENV::Number of training examples: 1469 Hence, effective training length: 1469 days
This is test Environment with 521 rows and 11 columns
ENV::Number of testing examples: 430 Hence, effective testing length: 430 days
Evaluation complete, plotting results
